[Music]
hello everyone i hope you're having a
lovely season so far
it was my birthday last weekend i turned
a quarter of a century and as
celebration i borrowed an old canoe and
went out on the water
[Music]
the lake is so still that it reflects
the clouds
my brother had a drone he let me use
while i was on the water
it never ceases to amaze me seeing
things from a bird's-eye perspective
the earth is so beautiful and so strange
the way it shifts and changes over
thousands of years
my valley used to be an enormous glacier
and now it's this
i can't begin to imagine what wondrous
thing it will become
i've never really been one for
celebrating my birthday even as a child
i preferred going to other people's
parties instead of having my own
but i still try to take a few moments to
say goodbye to one era and welcome the
next
the coming season holds within it a
hundred and more possibilities
i happen to have a couple friends who
are also december babies and they
describe this to be the starting point
of their quarter life crisis
i found this to be a very funny but apt
way to describe how most of us reach a
point in early adulthood when we begin
to seriously question who we are and
where we are going
[Music]
do
i remember for a while as a university
student i would follow my friends to
clubs and parties nearly every night
i wanted so desperately to feel like i
belonged
my friends enjoyed that environment and
it made them happy it was their best
space to relax and make memories
but it just wasn't really mine
i didn't like the deafening noise and
blurred memories going home and feeling
alone and anxious
it didn't suit my personality and it
took a long time to admit that to myself
particularly after i realized that that
lifestyle was feeding an addictive side
of my personality and not helping me
gain control over my life path
[Music]
while my lifestyle would have worked
very well for others it just wasn't the
best thing for me
i connected living that way as what made
me interesting and i think it's because
for many years i thought i just wasn't
interesting enough on my own
i wanted to label myself as someone i
wasn't
i think we often use labels in order to
feel like we belong when we're
inevitably more complicated than that
i think in a way it's very important to
have tough moments where we question
things to see ourselves better to choose
our friends with more care to admit how
complicated we are and that we don't
have things figured out
we have both darkness and light within
us we can feed the flame through living
the life that suits us best much like
bodies of water we have great potential
for depth to go deep and find what's
there yet often simply reflect our
environment
like the water we can always change over
time and recognize our own unique beauty
[Music]
someone once told me that everyone is
special
no one is more special than someone else
but we are nonetheless
i really like that it's a sweet
sentiment of recognizing what is sacred
in each of us
[Music]
as a side note i've recently started
dividing my videos the first half is my
usual content and then the last half i
get to talk to you directly in front of
the camera i've been enjoying it a lot
it's been really fun to share more
details and to connect with you all on a
more personal level so let me know if
you enjoy that and i will continue to do
it
[Music]
do
so i recorded this whole thing
and i was completely out of focus the
entire time i was completely blurry so
we're gonna try this again
if i sound really odd it's because i've
been coughing all day i don't know why
i'm not i don't feel sick but i've just
been coughing and
and my voice just sounds
really strange i've like aged
20 years anyway i hope you're all having
a wonderful day so far it's been a fun
week over here it was my birthday on
december 5th and on that day we didn't
have any snow barely any actually and
then
it came and and i think this is the
permanent snow for winter which is very
exciting during november the snow comes
and goes quite a bit and it just melts
away but but this is seems to be
sticking so
i'm i'm really excited i'm definitely
ready for full winter it is always
so beautiful over here as you can see
i've been having a lot of fun decorating
i always like to make at least a couple
wreaths or buy some wreaths this time of
year they are kind of my
uh for me they are the equivalent of a
christmas tree or a winter
tree and
while i love the way trees look in
houses i personally don't want to
kill one of the beautiful trees out here
because they're just so lovely and
i don't really want to bring them into
my home i really love how they look out
there especially when the snow falls on
them and i want to know that they're
going to be able to live many years i
got some very practical birthday
presents this year i was laughing i feel
like the older you get the more you just
want practical gifts instead of really
pretty things i i feel like that's maybe
it's just a me thing but i remember one
year i wanted art supplies and then the
next year after college all i wanted was
my
like groceries covered for that week so
it just became very boring but uh this
this year i really needed socks
so i got socks
i
noticed that pretty much every sock i
owned was just worn beyond repair and it
had a bunch of holes in it so my mother
was very happy to send me a lot of socks
i also desperately needed a new winter
jacket it's just really important to
have good
winter clothes
over here it's downright dangerous if
you don't and last year
i saved up and invested in a very very
nice
blue jacket that was very warm and i
absolutely loved it and i used it all
the time and then one day
i left a tiny piece of a dog biscuit
in my left pocket i forgot completely
about it
and my dog found my jacket and he
proceeded to
rip open the left half of the jacket to
find the dog treat and he ripped out a
bunch of stuffing and the pocket and he
opened the pocket and he got his dog
treat
but
yeah
the jacket was definitely
destroyed so
for my birthday i got myself a new
winter jacket and i definitely needed
one
and this one's definitely my favorite
it's very very warm
yes uh having a dog definitely creates a
lot of unforeseen and unexpected events
in your life um definitely some
inconveniences at times there is never a
dull moment with eiger i really don't
like
driving in the winter there's a lot of
ice on the roads and even though the
main roads are sanded a lot of the rural
roads just don't have anything really
and they're plowed but it can get really
icy and slippery and you have to wear
coverings on your boots so that you
don't slip on the ice and and i really
don't like driving it scares me a lot
there's a lot of deer here it's really
easy to hit a deer in summer
even more so in winter when you can't
stop the car quickly and so
i pretty much try to avoid
driving as little like i try to avoid
driving as much as possible one thing i
do to kind of avoid more trips to the
grocery store than i want is that i buy
a lot of bulk foods and i put them in
the pantry about this time of year
before the permanent snow comes
and i usually like to go to costco
because you can get a lot of bulk dry
goods for very little money and it's a
really great way for me to be able to
get some extra stuff and have it all
ready for the winter
sometimes you might get multiple feet of
snow within just a very short amount of
time and
if someone who plows isn't here quickly
you're pretty much just snowed in and
you have to wait and so it's really
important to have a lot of extra food
this time of year
i did have some dips in my health
last season and i've been trying to get
back on track with getting myself
back into the kitchen and making large
wholesome nutritious meals for myself
and i love to cook and bake and create
you know recipes
but sometimes if i'm working very much
or i'm in a rush i just don't take the
time to cook for myself i much prefer to
cook for other people
and so i've recently been using
a meal kit service to help me get
inspired and back into making some
recipes and some just kind of basic
meals for myself
and it's been really really helpful so
along with bulk items and some items
from the local grocery store i also get
some meal kits sent to me periodically
if i ever kind of need to get my health
back on track and so i usually only do
it for two or three weeks because it is
a bit expensive
but
it's much harder out here to kind of
have an in-person therapist or someone
to
help you with your diet and make sure
you're being very nutritionally
conscious and so
there just aren't that many resources
out here so that is one thing i do i
just try to invest a little more in
really quality food and to help me out
and the meal kit service has really
helped recently so
yeah that's what i've been doing i'll
leave a link down below i usually do i
think i've left a link in most of my
videos i'm just sharing it isn't none of
this is sponsored i pay for all of it
um yeah that's one of the reasons i
don't do it that much because it's a
little expensive the only reason i'm
sharing that information about the meal
kits is that it has really helped me
kind of get back on track when i am
tired or get out of the routine of
making good meals every night and really
uh doing wholesome wholesome meals so
maybe it will help you if you're in a
similar situation at any point so i just
thought i'd share i think that's it it's
getting dark really fast it's it's
always challenging to film this time of
year because there is so little daylight
and it just goes so quickly so
i'm on personally i am okay with it i do
like the night time it is really really
nice but
anyway i
hope you are all
doing well
if you're going to sleep i hope you have
some wonderful dreams
and i will see you next week
take care
goodbye